var title = "Enter the indefinite article (ένας, μία/μια, ένα)";

var questions = [

  {
    prompt: "__ καφές",
    answer: ["ένας"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "__ μάτι",
    answer: ["ένα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "__ γιατρός",
    answer: ["ένας"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "__ αρχή",
    answer: ["μία", "μια"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "__ παππούς",
    answer: ["ένας"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "__ διευθυντής",
    answer: ["ένας"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "__ πέλμα",
    answer: ["ένα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "__ πόρτα",
    answer: ["μία", "μια"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "__ ταμίας",
    answer: ["ένας"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "__ βιβλίο",
    answer: ["ένα"],
    partial: [],
  },

];
  